Guide to the Scott Green Collection of Speculative Fiction
Scott Green Collection of Speculative Fiction
1929-2007
1929 2007
Green Scott E.
RBC 00007
The Scott Green Collection of Speculative Fiction contains magazines, fanzines, review publications, newsletters, and other publications containing or related to speculative fiction, especially science fiction, fantasy, and horror. Many professional and amateur authors are well represented in this collection.
Poet and journalist Scott E. Green has been an active writer in a number of fields, including poetry, in the science fiction, fantasy, and horror genres. Green’s publications include his Contemporary Science Fiction, Fantasy, and Horror Poetry: A Resource Guide and Biographical Directory and Isaac Asimov: An Annotated Bibliography of the Asimov Collection at Boston University. His poetry has been published in numerous print and web publications including Aeon, Amazing, Astropoetica, Space and Time, Star*Line, Strange Horizons, and Writer’s Journal.
40.5 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Donated by Scott E. Green
This collection has not been fully processed. The materials are sorted by decade. Most of the materials are further arranged alphabetically by title, but some unsorted zines and other publications follow at the end of each decade for the 1970s, 1980s, and 1990s. The listing of a title indicates that there is at least one issue of that title in the box indicated. A small series of Avon Fantasy Readers and Avon Science Fiction Readers follows at the end of the collection.
Poet and journalist Scott E. Green earned his B.A. at Bates College in Asian history with a minor in government, and his M.A. in American history with a concentration in archives and museum management from Rhode Island College. He has been an active writer in a number of fields including poetry in the science fiction, fantasy, and horror genres. Green’s publications include his Contemporary Science Fiction, Fantasy, and Horror Poetry: A Resource Guide and Biographical Directory and Isaac Asimov: An Annotated Bibliography of the Asimov Collection at Boston University. His poetry has been published in numerous print and web publications including Aeon, Amazing, Astropoetica, Space and Time, Star*Line, Strange Horizons, and Writer’s Journal. Green served as president of the Science Fiction Poetry Association, served the National Writers Union in a variety of capacities, and maintained membership in the Science Fiction and Fantasy Writers of America.
The Scott Green Collection of Speculative Fiction contains magazines, fanzines, review publications, newsletters, and other publications containing or related to speculative fiction and poetry, especially the genres of science fiction, fantasy, and horror. Many professional and amateur authors are well represented in this collection.
Green Scott E.; Green Scott E.; Science fiction History and criticism; Science fiction poetry; Science fiction, American
- Amazing Stories, 1929-1939 (Carton 1)
- Argosy, 1929-1939 (Carton 1)
- Detective Fiction Weekly, 1929-1939 (Carton 1)
- Detective Tales, 1929-1939 (Carton 1)
- Dynamic Science Stories, 1929-1939 (Carton 1)
- Galaxy Novel Odd John, 1929-1939 (Carton 1)
- Science Fiction, 1929-1939 (Carton 1)
- Startling Stories, 1929-1939 (Carton 1)
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1929-1939 (Carton 1)
- Weird Tales, 1929-1939 (Carton 1)
- Wonder Stories, 1929-1939 (Carton 1)
- A. Merritt's Fantasy, 1940-1949 (Carton 1)
- Amazing Stories, 1940-1949 (Carton 1)
- Astonishing Stories, 1940-1949 (Carton 1)
- Famous Fantastic Mysteries, 1940-1949 (Carton 1)
- Famous Fantastic Mysteries, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Fantastic Adventures, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Fantastic Novels, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Fantasy Book, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Fantasy Review, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Future Fiction, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Galaxy Novel The Black Galaxy, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Galaxy Novel The Rat Race, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Myrddin Two, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- New Worlds, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Other Worlds, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Spicy Adventure Stories, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Startling Stories, 1940-1949 (Carton 2)
- Super Science Stories, 1940-1949 (Carton 3)
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1940-1949 (Carton 3)
- Unknown Worlds, 1940-1949 (Carton 3)
- Weird Tales, 1940-1949 (Carton 3)
- A. Merritt's Fantasy, 1950-1959 (Carton 3)
- Amazing Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 3)
- Antares, 1950-1959 (Carton 3)
- Astounding Science Fiction, 1950-1959 (Carton 3)
- Authentic Science Fiction, 1950-1959 (Carton 3)
- Beyond, 1950-1959 (Carton 3)
- Beyond, 1950-1959 (Carton 4)
- Cosmos, 1950-1959 (Carton 4)
- Destiny, 1950-1959 (Carton 4)
- Dreamworld, 1950-1959 (Carton 4)
- Dynamic, 1950-1959 (Carton 4)
- Famous Fantastic Mysteries, 1950-1959 (Carton 4)
- Fantastic Adventures, 1950-1959 (Carton 4)
- Fantastic Novels, 1950-1959 (Carton 4)
- Fantastic Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 4)
- Fantastic Universe, 1950-1959 (Carton 4)
- Fantastic Universe, 1950-1959 (Carton 5)
- Fantasy Book, 1950-1959 (Carton 5)
- Fantasy Fiction Magazine, 1950-1959 (Carton 5)
- Future, 1950-1959 (Carton 5)
- Future, 1950-1959 (Carton 6)
- Galaxy, 1950-1959 (Carton 6)
- Imagination, 1950-1959 (Carton 6)
- Imaginative Tales, 1950-1959 (Carton 6)
- Infinity, 1950-1959 (Carton 6)
- Marvel, 1950-1959 (Carton 7)
- Nebula, 1950-1959 (Carton 7)
- New Worlds, 1950-1959 (Carton 7)
- Orbit, 1950-1959 (Carton 7)
- Other Worlds, 1950-1959 (Carton 7)
- Planet, 1950-1959 (Carton 7)
- Rocket Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 7)
- Satellite, 1950-1959 (Carton 7)
- Saturn, 1950-1959 (Carton 7)
- Saturn, 1950-1959 (Carton 8)
- Science Adventure, 1950-1959 (Carton 8)
- Science Fantasy, 1950-1959 (Carton 8)
- Science Fiction Adventures, 1950-1959 (Carton 8)
- Science Fiction and Fantasy Reader, 1950-1959 (Carton 8)
- Science Fiction Classics, 1950-1959 (Carton 8)
- Science Fiction Digest, 1950-1959 (Carton 8)
- Science Fiction Plus, 1950-1959 (Carton 8)
- Science Fiction Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 8)
- Science Fiction Quarterly, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Science Fiction Quarterly, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Science Fiction Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Science Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Short Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Space Science Fiction, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Space Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Spaceway, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Star Science Fiction, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Startling Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Strange Science Fiction, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Super Science Fiction, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Super Science Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 9)
- Startling Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 10)
- Suspense, 1950-1959 (Carton 10)
- Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 10)
- Universe, 1950-1959 (Carton 10)
- Vangaurd, 1950-1959 (Carton 10)
- Venture, 1950-1959 (Carton 10)
- Void, 1950-1959 (Carton 10)
- Vortex, 1950-1959 (Carton 10)
- Weird Tales, 1950-1959 (Carton 10)
- Weird Tales, 1950-1959 (Carton 11)
- Wonder Stories, 1950-1959 (Carton 11)
- Wonder Story Annual, 1950-1959 (Carton 11)
- Worlds Beyond, 1950-1959 (Carton 11)
- Worlds Beyond, 1950-1959 (Carton 11)
- Anubis, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Argosy, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Arkham Collector, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Bizarre, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Coven 13, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Edgar Wallace, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Famous Science Fiction, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Fantastic Universe, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Fantasy Collector, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Future Science Fiction, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Galaxy Novel Three Go Back, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Gamma, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Great Science Fiction, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Horror, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- International Science Fiction, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Man From U.N.C.L.E., 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- Most Thrilling Science Fiction, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- New Worlds, 1960-1969 (Carton 11)
- New Worlds, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Niekas, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Riverside Quarterly, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Science Fantasy, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Science Fiction Adventure Classics, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Science Fiction Classics, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- SF Impulse, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Shock, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Spaceway, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Startling Mystery Stories, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Vanguard, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Venture, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Weird Book, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Weird Terror, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Worlds of Fantasy, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Worlds of Tomorrow, 1960-1969 (Carton 12)
- Worlds of Tomorrow, 1960-1969 (Carton 13)
- Adastra, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Algol/Starship Algol/Starship, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Argosy UFO, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Arkham Collector, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Cosmos, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Coven 13, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Delany, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Destiny of Science Fiction, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Emprire for the SF Writer, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Eternity, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Fantastic Films, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Fantasy Tales, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Forgotten Fantasy, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Haunt of Horror, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Lost Fantasies, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Magazine of Horror, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Magic Carpet, 1970-1979 (Carton 13)
- Mike Shayne, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Night Voyages, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Oddysey, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Official UFO, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Pandora, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Pretentious Science Fiction Quarterly, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Riverside Quarterly, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Science Fiction Adventures, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Science Fiction Adventures Magazine, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Science Fiction Collector, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Science Fiction Monthly, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Science Fiction Review, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Science Fiction Review Monthly, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Science Fiction Times, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- SF Commentary, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Shayol, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Space and Time, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Startling Mystery Stories, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Strange Fantasy, 1970-1979 (Carton 14)
- Talisman, 1970-1979 (Carton 15)
- Thrilling Science Fiction, 1970-1979 (Carton 15)
- Unearth, 1970-1979 (Carton 15)
- Venture, 1970-1979 (Carton 15)
- Vertex, 1970-1979 (Carton 15)
- Vision, 1970-1979 (Carton 15)
- Weird Book, 1970-1979 (Carton 15)
- Weird Tales, 1970-1979 (Carton 15)
- Worlds of Tomorrow, 1970-1979 (Carton 15)
- Assorted zines and other publications, 1970-1979 (Carton 15)
- Assorted zines and other publications, 1970-1979 (Carton 16)
- 2 A.M., 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Aboriginal Science Fiction, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Adastra, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- After Hours, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- American Fantasy, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Antares, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Argonaut, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Argos, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Arkham Sampler, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Bantha Tracks, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Beyond, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Celestial Visions, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Dragon, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Eldritch Tales, 1980-1989 (Carton 16)
- Empire Waystation, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Espionage, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Eternity, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Event Horizon, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Fantasy Book, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Fantasy Empire, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Fantasy F and SF News Monthly, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Fantasy Newsletter, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Fantasy Review, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Fantasy Tales, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Fear, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Grue, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Haunts, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Marion Simmer Bradley's Fantasy, 1980-1989 (Carton 17)
- Horror Show, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Horror Struck, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Interzone, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Just Pulp, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Kadath Weird and Fantasy Fiction, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Last Wave, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Leading Edge, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Looking Glass, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Magazine of Speculative Poetry, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Megavore 10, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Midnight Graffiti, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- New Blood, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- New Pathways, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Nickelodeon Exotic Science Fiction and Fantasy Quarterly, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Nickelodeon Exotic Science Fiction and Fantasy Quarterly, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Niekas, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Night Cry, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Night Voyages, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Nova Express, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Other Gates, 1980-1989 (Carton 18)
- Pandora, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Poetry Mag, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Pretentious Science Fiction Quarterly, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Questar, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Rigel, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Science Fiction Chronicle, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Science Fiction Collector, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Science Fiction Digest, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Science Fiction Review, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- SF Commentary, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Shadows of..., 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Shayol, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Silver Griffin, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Space and Time, 1980-1989 (Carton 19)
- Sorcerer's Apprentice, 1980-1989 (Carton 20)
- Stardate, 1980-1989 (Carton 20)
- Starline, 1980-1989 (Carton 20)
- Starship, 1980-1989 (Carton 20)
- Tales of the Unanticipated, 1980-1989 (Carton 20)
- Thrust, 1980-1989 (Carton 20)
- Tri-Quarterly 49, 1980-1989 (Carton 20)
- Twilight Zone Magazine, 1980-1989 (Carton 20)
- Twilight Zone Magazine, 1980-1989 (Carton 21)
- Velocities Cartoned Set, 1980-1989 (Carton 21)
- Weird Tales, 1980-1989 (Carton 21)
- Whispers, 1980-1989 (Carton 21)
- Wired Journal, 1980-1989 (Carton 21)
- World Journal, 1980-1989 (Carton 21)
- Assorted zines and other publications, 1980-1989 (Carton 21)
- Assorted zines and other publications, 1980-1989 (Carton 22)
- Aboriginal Science Fiction, 1990-1999 (Carton 22)
- 14th Alternative, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Absolute Magnitude, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Adventures of Sword and Sorcery, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- After Hours, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Alternate Hilarities, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Anticipatia, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Argosy, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- ASI, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Astromancer Quarterly, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Beyond, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Bizarre Bazaar, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Blood Lines, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Boing Boing, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Cemetery Dancer, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Century, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Challenge 55, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Challenging Destiny, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Churchyard: An Anthology of Christian Weird Tales, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Crank, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Cursor Game Development Life, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Dead of Night, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Death Realm, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Dream Watch, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Dreams and Nightmares, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Dumars Review, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- DWB, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Edge Detector, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- El Wendigo, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Eldritch Science, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Epi-log, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Expanse, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Fantastic Collectibles, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Fantastic Images, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Fantasy Illustrated, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Fantasy Magazine, 1990-1999 (Carton 23)
- Fantasy Tales, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Far and Away, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Fear, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Fifth Di--, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Filmfax, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Forbidden Lines, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Games Workshop White Dwarf, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Gateway, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Gauntlet, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Genre Press Digest, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Genre Sampler, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Genre Writer's News, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Grue, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Harsh Mistress, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Haunts, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- High Adventure, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Horror, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Ikarie, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Inequities, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Interaction, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Interzone, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Kinships, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Kit Builders, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Lost, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Midnight Graffiti, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Mindsparks, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Movie Club, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Next Phase, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Nexus, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Nightmares, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Non-Stop, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Nova Express, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- On-Spec, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Orphia, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Paper Mayhem, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Perry Rhodan, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Pirate Writings, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Pulp House, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- R.E.M., 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Realms of Fantasy, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Remark, 1990-1999 (Carton 24)
- Report, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Retro, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Scarlett Sheet, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Scary Monsters, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Sci-Fi Entertainment, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Science Fiction Age, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Science Fiction Chronicle, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Science Fiction Review, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Scream Factory, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Silvery Web, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Sixth Sense, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Sol Rising, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Somnium, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Space and Time, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Star Anthology, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Star Burst, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Star Flight, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Star*Line, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Star Quest, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Star Shore, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Strange Days, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Strange Magazine, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Strange New Worlds, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Strange Plasma, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Stroke and Dagger, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Tales of the Unanticipated, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Tangent, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Terminal Fright, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Thirteenth Moon, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Tome, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Tomorrow, 1990-1999 (Carton 25)
- Tomorrow, 1990-1999 (Carton 26)
- Touch, 1990-1999 (Carton 26)
- Tyro, 1990-1999 (Carton 26)
- Vision, 1990-1999 (Carton 26)
- Vortext, 1990-1999 (Carton 26)
- Weird Tales, 1990-1999 (Carton 26)
- White Wolf Magazine, 1990-1999 (Carton 26)
- Xizquil, 1990-1999 (Carton 26)
- Zero Gravity Freefall, 1990-1999 (Carton 26)
- Assorted zines and other publications, 1990-1999 (Carton 26)
- Assorted zines and other publications, 1990-1999 (Carton 27)
- 3 SF, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Adventures of Sword and Sorcery, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Artemis, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Dark Illuminati, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Dreams and Nightmares, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Electric Velocipede, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Futures, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Gauntlet, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- H.P. Lovecraft's Magazine of Horror, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Inhuman, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Journal of Pulse-Pounding Narratives, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Mind's Eye Theater Journal, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- New Genre, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Nth Degree, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Oceans of the Mind, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Paradox, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Rosebud, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Scared Naked Magazine, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Starline, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Tarpeian Rock, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Temple, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Weird Tales, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Year 2000, 2000-2007 (Carton 27)
- Avon Fantasy Reader no. 1-18, 1947-1952 (Carton 27)
- Avon Science Fiction Reader no. 1-3, 1951-1952 (Carton 27)